All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict.
This will be destroyed. And quickly. We'll rebuild it from scratch. But with a new king. Like me.
Citizens of Fishman Island, the old Ryugu Kingdom has worn out its welcome.
Time to say goodbye.
In three hours, at the Conchcord Plaza, the weak and incompetent King Neptune will be put to death.
Straw Hat, I know. You're there. I have something that may be of interest to you.
As you watch from wherever you are, I want you to know that this is just the beginning of my revenge for what you did to Arla. Enjoy.
Oh man! He even captured Zoro?!
Why do we leave them alone?
But still, all three?
It's water!
By the time we finish the king's execution, that room will be completely flooded.
You lowly humans can't survive that, if I'm not mistaken. Too bad.
Hey, Shark! Take me back to the palace!
Yeah!
Luffy! I told you to wait!
Huh?
You don't get it! You people have no business fighting Horden!
You're wrong! Not when my crew's in trouble!
It's not that I don't trust you, but this fight is personal for me, too!
Such a stubborn fool!
You shut up already! If you don't want me to go, then stop me!
Since we were allies before, I had hoped that you would honor my request.
How easily I forget who you are! Hard-headedness truly does run in your family!
Stand down, Luffy! Or else!
The Rift opens up! Luffy vs. Jinbei!
Have I told you what people called me? I was the submarine of the East Blue!
That's cause I could swim an 82-foot pool in no time at all!
82 feet? I could run over a pool that tiny!
That's one advantage to being a skeleton! I'm light as air!
You know what? We should have a race one of these days to see which one of us is faster!
Any time you're in the mood to lose, I'll be more than happy to let you eat my dust!
That is if we ever get out of here!
Yeah, this is not looking good for us!
After all that training, crowning is a seriously my way to go!
Anything for a watery grave?
Shut up!
Hey, how is it you can sit there with your eyes closed like nothing's going on?
Oh, I know. You must be coming up with a plan to set us free!
Nope.
You couldn't have lied!
You'll be honest to the bitter end!
Wow!
Everything would be fine if I had a sword!
I don't think that's true.
Things have gotten bleak.
I didn't want to do this in front of you, but so be it.
Uh, do what exactly?
Okay, Brook, you're really starting to freak me out here!
Stop! That's enough!
No!
Kaboom!
And I'm out!
Well, good luck, you guys!
Wait a damn second!
Huh?
You're just gonna leave without explaining or anything?
Since when have you been able to do something like this freaky crap?
What? You mean make my soul leave my body?
Yeah, I thought only real dead people did that!
It's a new trick.
I was surprised.
It first happened on my world tour as Soul King quite suddenly.
During that time, I had fallen into a dreadful slump.
The sales of my TDs and concert tickets were on the decline.
I wasn't sure what I should do to stay relevant.
Bummer.
Today's show wasn't groovy at all, was it?
Hate to say it, but I liked his old music better.
It's like, I don't feel his soul anymore.
What the hell's happening to you, Brooke?
If you don't write a song that sells, I'm cutting you loose!
I'm trying, I promise.
But it's not that easy.
Music isn't something you simply throw together.
Maybe I'm forsaken, and the god of music doesn't smile upon me anymore.
I beg of you, let me write one last good song.
Oh, please.
Bless me, god of music.
Grant me a melody that will shake all who hear it to their souls.
Please.
What's going on?!
It was frightening at first, but it really helped.
With this new ability came an epiphany.
I finally realized what was missing from my music and how to get out of my slump.
to get out of my slum, which was...
Well, it's actually pretty obvious
when you think about it.
If a man can go anywhere undetected,
there's one thing he's going to go looking for.
He's so lucky, Zoro.
Why can't I be dead like he is?
Really?
Hey, the water's gotten so high,
soon you will be dead like me.
You just had to remind me, didn't you?
Hurry up and do something!
Please, you two, try to calm down.
Luffy! Jinbei!
This is no time for you guys to act like
you're going to kill each other!
Get out of my way! I gotta go save my friends!
And when I'm done, I'm kicking Hordy's ass!
I told you not to get involved with him, Luffy!
Whoa, hey, surely there's a better way
to work this out.
Yeah, stop it, both of you!
Luffy, please!
I don't want my friends to fight!
Shark! Let's go!
Get me back to the palace!
Ah!
You'll have to go through me first!
Right, fine by me!
Fishman Caratter!
The Shark Brickfish!
What?
Oh, no!
That looks bad!
Ah!
That hurt!
What?
No way!
He's made of rubber!
Attacks like that shouldn't even work on him!
But this is Fishman Karate!
A form based on manipulating water!
I can send shockwaves through vapor in the air
until they finally find my target's body!
Seeing as every living creature is made up of water,
not even a rubber man can escape the impact!
You shall not pass, Luffy!
Second gear!
Now come, come!
Jack!
After so much training, don't tell me that's all you've got!
Not a chance!
Enough of that!
Rockin!
You're back!
Hey!
Get out of the way!
Now!
Move it!
You'll die!
Don't worry!
I'll save you!
There's no need to fight.
I'm sure you both have your reasons, but you're friends, right?
Wait! You mean Robin's been in the forest this entire time?
Take this!
Give it up already, alright? You guys don't stand a chance against us!
Are you crazy?
What, did you not see Boss Horty's broadcast before?
This country's gonna burn.
And Neptune is gonna die!
Why, you!
Stop!
Spare them their lives.
If you do not, you will be no better than they are.
But, but, sir!
Ryuboshi, Momboshi, take them into custody.
Count on me, Redo!
Say, Bill!
I see you're as weak-willed as ever.
But I guess that yellow belly of yours does run in the royal family, doesn't it?
How dare you?
It was reprehensible to harm humans.
Now you assault your own kind?
Does your heart not weep in regrets?
Of course it doesn't, because any fish man who willingly sides with humans deserves nothing less than execution.
So why don't we start with you, FUKABUCHI!
Have it your way, then!
And yet...
That hurts!
There are none of these games in contrast to the Coalition.
The new galaxy will look at all the glory of the original faxure.
Technical ACLU
activates a blessed человека
Active hope for the original faxure.
When the battle stopped again, it won't lose.
Action and patience is alreadyphones
The last big zear.
delight in elters
mushed
Damn it! How'd we lose?
Yeah! I never doubted the three royal brothers for a second!
Thank you, Prince Fugaboshi!
My lord, please leave the rest to us.
Much appreciated. We must hurry to Conchcord Plaza in order to prevent our father's execution.
All right, let's go!
Well, it's about time we got this show underway.
Do you want some of us to stay and protect the palace while you're gone, Boss Horty?
No need. But don't you remember?
No one else can get through the palace gate.
We'll station a handful of men here to make sure someone's around to open it when I return.
After all, you can't lock out the new king.
That'd be a shame!
More like nonsense.
You will never be respected as king if you rule through violence.
Is that really what you want your last words to be? I'd have gone for something strong.
My scar, it's burning. I can't believe that stupid human swordsman actually managed to cut me.
It's wearing off. Hey, it's time for my next dose.
Now I feel as good as new. Isn't it dangerous taking that much at once?
I thought so.
Hey, Captain. What do we do with the three straw hats we captured?
Nothing. They're just humans. They'll drown if left alone. And the palace is secure so no one will be able to rescue them regardless of who comes.
Forget them. Now what's the current status of the residents from the fishman district that we recruited today?
They're doing just fine. In fact, they should be making their move as we speak.
That's good. Pretty soon they'll be out of the slums. Seeing as once all of the traitors have left or been killed, there'll be plenty of houses on the market.
Then our country will finally be united in its hatred for the pathetic human race.
I think I found it, guys. A bright ray of hope.
Listen, those fishmen we were dealing with earlier have left so the palace is completely empty.
Or rather, it would be if they hadn't left Papagu behind.
That's awesome, Brooke. Now we just need to ask Papagu to find the keys to get us out of these chains.
I guess we need the one to unlock this cage, too.
Don't be an idiot. Just find one of my swords. That's all we really need to escape.
I'll cut anything in my way.
Yeah! That's all you ever want to do!
All right! I'm off to search for Papagu!
Yo-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
I am freaking out! Why did this have to happen? Come have a banquet, they said. It'll be fun!
I hope the straw hats are okay.
I am the only one who's ready.
Ah!
PAPA GU!
No!
At last, you're a ghost!
Where is my friend?
I hate this place!
Stop, Papago!
I need your help!
Find the keys, please!
The sword!
Go find the sword!
Go away! I don't know what you're talking about!
Hey!
Are you guys okay?
Need a doctor?
Think, Luffy.
Have you considered what will happen if you resort to violence while on Fishman Island?
Every time my people have tried to reach out and open their hearts to humans, they have been met with nothing but disappointment and prejudice.
Humans like to make us suffer.
Humans hate fishmen.
They look down on us.
Don't you see?
This is what our citizens have come to believe because of the horrible things that have happened in our past.
And Arlong is a perfect example.
The people here believe that the humans hunted him when he went to the surface solely because he was a fishman.
And now you, the people who suppressed Arlong are here.
What will the islanders think if you crush Hordy as well?
Misguided though he may be, Hordy's aim is to fight against persecution.
So even if it saves us from this crisis in the long run, if they see a group of humans attacking him,
it will only solidify the idea that things will never change between us.
Oh well, that's too bad.
You're crazy if you think we won't rescue our crew.
And unless we do something soon, Hordy's going to take over the whole island.
And that's a problem because we have a lot of friends that live here.
Like Hachi.
Yeah.
You've kept pretty quiet about who banged you up so bad.
But now that I think about it,
you mentioned before that Hordy attacks any fishman that sympathizes with humans.
So...
I guess the reason you're in that sorry state is because you spoke up for us, right?
Yeah...
Why?
Hachi!
Is that true?
Hordy did this to you?
I can't say.
Jinbei, with all that in mind, I'm pretty sure Luffy wants to fight so bad because this is your home too.
When our captain's back was against the wall, you were the one who was there to help him.
For that, there's no way we'll ever be able to thank you enough.
But if Luffy wants to fight, we'll fight with him whatever it takes.
We won't be able to leave the island like this.
We can't turn a blind eye.
There's too much at stake.
We're taking a stand.
Because Kimi's here!
And Shou Hoshi too!
See? This island is the mermaid paradise I've always dreamed of!
Get out of my way, Jinbei.
I won't let you keep me here anymore!
Let me handle it!
You stay put!
Shut up!
Sanji said all that cool stuff and you still wanna fight?!
If that is what it takes to make you listen to me, yes!
What did you say?!
Ugh, not at all!
You stay put!
Neptune's execution draws nigh, but Luffy and Jinbei have yet to settle their differences.
As the new Fishman pirates spread across the island, it seems that they have won the battle without a hint of resistance.
But Horty himself is experiencing a strange side effect of the energy steroids, as his body undergoes a horrifying transformation.
On the next, One Piece, something has happened to Horty!
The true power of the evil Drog, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!